A Guide to the W. W. LaPrade and Brothers Records, 1803-2001 (bulk 1900-1970)
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Ernest W. Brooks files, 1953-1979., Extent: 7 boxes. (Box 176-182)
  The files were maintained in their original order and may require the researcher to consult all files pertaining to a county to obtain a specific plat. There is much overlap between the two subseries. Researchers also need to check the Oversize Series (Boxes 93-95) for additional Brooks and W. S. Hinton files.
  Arranged into two subseries consisting of Alphabetical and Numerical files.
  - Subseries 1. Alphabetical files., 2 boxes (2 cu. ft.) (Box 176-177)
    This subseries was arranged alphabetically by county, beginning with Chesterfield, Henrico, and Hanover Counties, and Richmond, followed by miscellaneous counties. The miscellaneous counties include Amelia, Caroline, Charles City, Essex, Gloucester, Goochland, King and Queen, New Kent, Powhatan, and York Counties, Virginia.
    The files within each county are arranged alphabetically by street name. For example if looking for a plat of Bellwood Avenue in Richmond, search under Richmond, B (Box 177, Folder 28).
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 1)
      A-B
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 2)
      C-D
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 3)
      E-F
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 4)
      G-H
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176)
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 5)
      I-J
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 6)
      K-L
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 7)
      M-N
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 8)
      O-P
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 9)
      Q-R
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 10)
      S-T
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 11)
      U-V
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 12)
      W-X
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 13)
      Route 10: Bermuda, Dale, and Midlothian districts
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 14)
      U.S. Routes 60, 360: Clover Hill, Manchester, and Midlothian districts
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 15)
      Route 602: Clover Hill and Matoaca districts
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 16)
      Route 621: Clover Hill district
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 17)
      Routes 600-650: Clover Hill, Dale, Matoaca, and Midlothian districts
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 18)
      Routes 651-699: Clover Hill and Midlothian districts
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 19)
      Routes 700-799: Clover Hill and Midlothian districts
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 20)
      Covendale Section A: Bermuda district
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 21)
      Glen Wood: Clover Hill district
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 22)
      Genito Forest: Clover Hill district
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 23)
      Loch Braemar: Clover Hill district
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 176, Folder 24)
      Providence Glen: Clover Hill district
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 25)
      A
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 26)
      B
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 27)
      C
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 28)
      D
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 29)
      E
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 30)
      F
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 31)
      G
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 32)
      H
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 33)
      I
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 34)
      J
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 35)
      K
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 36)
      L
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 37)
      M
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 38)
      N
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 39)
      O
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 40)
      P
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 41)
      R
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 42)
      S
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 43)
      T
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 44)
      U
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 45)
      V
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 46)
      W
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 47)
      Y
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 48)
      Z
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 49)
      Countryside: Tuckahoe district
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 50)
      Higginbotham property, River Road
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 51)
      Kingsland Manor: Varina district
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 52)
      Meadowood, Sections 1-4: Brookland district
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 53)
      Meadowood, Section 5: Brookland district
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 54)
      Pemberton Town houses: Tuckahoe district
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 55)
      Sleepy Hollow: Tuckahoe district
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 56)
    - Henrico Co. (Box 176, Folder 57)
      Correspondence, 1970-1971
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 11)
      W-Z
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 12)
      U.S. Route 1 and 54
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 13)
      Atlee Manor
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 14)
      Route 156
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 15)
      U.S. Route 301
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 16)
      U.S. Route 360
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 17)
      Routes 600-650
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 18)
      Routes 651-699
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 19)
      Routes 700-799
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 20)
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 21)
      Brandy Creek Estates
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 22)
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 23)
      Ellerson Farms
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 24)
      Holly Ridge A and B
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 25)
      Strawhorn
    - Hanover Co. (Box 177, Folder 26)
      Walnut Grove
    - Richmond (Box 177, Folder 27)
    - Richmond (Box 177, Folder 28)
    - Richmond (Box 177, Folder 29)
    - Richmond (Box 177, Folder 30)
    - Richmond (Box 177, Folder 31)
    - Richmond (Box 177, Folder 32)
      H-K
    - Richmond (Box 177, Folder 33)
      L-M
    - Richmond (Box 177, Folder 34)
      N-P
    - Richmond (Box 177, Folder 35)
    - Richmond (Box 177, Folder 36)
    - Richmond (Box 177, Folder 37)
      V-Z
    - Amelia Co. (Box 177, Folder 38)
    - Blacksburg (Box 177, Folder 39)
    - Caroline Co. (Box 177, Folder 40)
    - Charles City Co. (Box 177, Folder 41)
    - Essex Co. (Box 177, Folder 42)
    - Gloucester Co. (Box 177, Folder 43)
    - Goochland Co. (Box 177, Folder 44)
    - King and Queen Co. (Box 177, Folder 45)
    - New Kent Co. (Box 177, Folder 46)
    - Powhatan Co. (Box 177, Folder 47)
    - York Co. (Box 177, Folder 48)
  - Subseries 2. Numerical files., 5 boxes (5 cu. ft.) (Box 178-182)
    This subseries is arranged numerically with Miscellaneous numbered plats filed first, followed by Job number files. The miscellaneous numbered plats are grouped by county (Chesterfield and Henrico) and Richmond and then arranged numerically 1-1000. Unfortunately information explaining the numerical system of these files does not exist. The plats were in boxes marked, Property of Policy Writing Dept., and seem to have corresponding labels, CPB are Chesterfield plats, HPB are Henrico plats, and RPB are Richmond plats. Again, researchers interested in specific plats should consult all the files for the county.
    The Job number files are arranged numerically and include not only plats from Brooks, but also some plats from LaPrade and Foster and Miller. Files without job numbers are located at the end, grouped together by county.
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 178, Folder 1)
      CPB 2-100
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 178, Folder 2)
      CPB 101-199
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 178, Folder 3)
      CPB 201-299
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 178, Folder 4)
      CPB 301-399
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 178, Folder 5)
      CPB 400-491
    - Henrico Co. (Box 178, Folder 6)
      HPB 1-99
    - Henrico Co. (Box 178, Folder 7)
      HPB 100-199
    - Henrico Co. (Box 178, Folder 8)
      HPB 200-299
    - Henrico Co. (Box 178, Folder 9)
      HPB 300-399
    - Henrico Co. (Box 178, Folder 10)
      HPB 400-450
    - Henrico Co. (Box 178, Folder 11)
      451-499
    - Henrico Co. (Box 178, Folder 12)
      HPB 500-599
    - Henrico Co. (Box 178, Folder 13)
      HPB 600-699
    - Henrico Co. (Box 178, Folder 14)
      HPB 700-1006
    - Richmond (Box 179, Folder 1)
      RPB 1-99
    - Richmond (Box 179, Folder 2)
      RPB 100-199
    - Richmond (Box 179, Folder 3)
      RPB 200-299
    - Richmond (Box 179, Folder 4)
      RPB 300-399
    - Richmond (Box 179, Folder 5)
      RPB 400-439
    - Richmond (Box 179, Folder 6)
      No RPB number, Lots in Home Place
    - Job no. 100. (Box 180, Folder 1)
      U.S. Route 360, King and Queen Co.
    - Job no. 101. (Box 180, Folder 2)
      State Route 6.81, Trueheart tract, Amelia Co.
    - Job no. 103. (Box 180, Folder 3)
      River Road, Route 602, Matoaca district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 104. (Box 180, Folder 4)
      Henry Street, Route 1301, Hanover Co.
    - Job no. 110. (Box 180, Folder 5)
      Nash Road, State Route 636, Matoaca district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 111. (Box 180, Folder 6)
      Jessup Road, Brettwood Place, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 112. (Box 180, Folder 7)
      U.S. Route 1, Colonial Heights
    - Job no. 113. (Box 180, Folder 8)
      Raven Wood Road, Sleepy Hollow, Tuckahoe district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 115. (Box 180, Folder 9)
      State Route 600, Caroline Co.
    - Job no. 117 (Box 180, Folder 10)
      Routes 609 and 630, Amelia Co.
    - Job no. 118. (Box 180, Folder 11)
      Bevils Bridge Rd., Cedar Creek Road, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 119. (Box 180, Folder 12-13)
      Route 360, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co., Speeks family
    - Job no. 120. (Box 180, Folder 14)
      State Route 654, Goochland Co.
    - Job no. 121. (Box 180, Folder 15)
      Area east of Route 301
    - Job no. 123. (Box 180, Folder 16)
      Mullins Lane, Fairfield district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 125. (Box 180, Folder 17)
      Chamberlayne Ave., Richmond
    - Job no. 126. (Box 180, Folder 18)
      Rodney Road, Three Chopt district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 127. (Box 180, Folder 19)
      Varina Road, Varina district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 129. (Box 180, Folder 20)
      Routes 652 and 607, Midlothian district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 131. (Box 180, Folder 21)
      Route 522, Powhatan Co.
    - Job no. 133. (Box 180, Folder 22)
      Kensington Ave., Richmond
    - Job no. 134. (Box 180, Folder 23)
      Francis Road, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 135. (Box 180, Folder 24)
      Route 623, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 139. (Box 180, Folder 25)
      Route 602, Caroline Co.
    - Job no. 144. (Box 180, Folder 26)
      Route 616, Powhatan Co.
    - Job no. 148. (Box 180, Folder 27)
      Nuckols Road, Three Chopt district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 150. (Box 180, Folder 28)
      Nine Mile Road, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 162. (Box 180, Folder 29)
      Near Route 611, New Kent Co.
    - Job no. 167. (Box 180, Folder 30)
      Route 668, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 168. (Box 180, Folder 31)
      Route 301, Hanover Co.
    - Job no. 171. (Box 180, Folder 32)
      Route 623, Hanover Co.
    - Job no. 174. (Box 180, Folder 33)
      Route 621, Powhatan Co.
    - Job no. 175. (Box 180, Folder 34)
      Greenwood Road, Brookland district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 177. (Box 180, Folder 35)
      Providence Road, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 179. (Box 180, Folder 36)
      Parham Road and Hooper Road, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 188. (Box 180, Folder 37)
      Near Route 708, between Route 612 and 600, Amelia Co.
    - Job no. 201. (Box 180, Folder 38)
    - Job no. 207. (Box 180, Folder 39)
      Route 693, Gloucester Co.
    - Job no. 210. (Box 180, Folder 40)
      Courthouse Road, Midlothian district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 211. (Box 180, Folder 41)
      Route 678, Goochland Co.
    - Job no. 213. (Box 180, Folder 42)
      Lakeside Avenue and Vale Street, Brookland district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 224. (Box 180, Folder 43)
      River Road, Matoaca district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 225. (Box 180, Folder 44)
      Graves Road and River Road, Matoaca district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 228. (Box 180, Folder 45)
      Stuart Avenue, Richmond
    - Job no.. (Box 180, Folder 46)
      Sleepy Hollow, Tuckahoe district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 231. (Box 180, Folder 47)
      Route 643, Rural Point Road, Hanover Co.
    - Job no. 233. (Box 180, Folder 48)
      Westham Parkway, Tuckahoe district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 234. (Box 181, Folder 1)
      Route 628, Powhatan Co.
    - Job no. 235. (Box 181, Folder 2)
      Off Route 694, Caroline Co.
    - Job no. 236 (Box 181, Folder 3)
      Route 621, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 237. (Box 181, Folder 4)
      Broad Street and Colyer Avenue, Woodlawn Farms, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 238. (Box 181, Folder 5)
      Coalboro Road, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 239. (Box 181, Folder 6)
      Route 22 and 33, Louisa Co.
    - Job no. 240. (Box 181, Folder 7)
      Route 686, Hanover Co.
    - Job no. 245 and 260. (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Job no. 248. (Box 181, Folder 9)
      Chamberlayne and Wilmer Avenues, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 253. (Box 181, Folder 10)
      Ryan Rd., Brookland district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 254. (Box 181, Folder 11)
      Doverland Road, Sleepy Hollow, Tuckahoe district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 262. (Box 181, Folder 12)
      Avondale Road, Richmond
    - Job no. 265. (Box 181, Folder 13)
      Route 646, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 267. (Box 181, Folder 14)
      Route 671, Amelia Co.
    - Job no. 279. (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - Job no. 280. (Box 181, Folder 16)
      Mountain Road and Route 1, Brookland district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 286. (Box 181, Folder 17)
      Route 611, Goochland Co.
    - Job no. 288. (Box 181, Folder 18)
      Route 643, Amelia Co.
    - Job no. 297. (Box 181, Folder 19)
      Route 612, Goochland Co.
    - Job no. 298. (Box 181, Folder 20)
      Route 54, Hanover Co.
    - Job no. 301. (Box 181, Folder 21)
    - Job no. 303. (Box 181, Folder 22)
      Route 681, Amelia Co.
    - Job no. 306. (Box 181, Folder 23)
      Auburn Chase, Goochland Co.
    - Job no. 309. (Box 181, Folder 24)
    - Job no. 312. (Box 181, Folder 25)
      Route 360, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 313. (Box 181, Folder 26)
      Route 607, Amelia Co.
    - Job no. 320. (Box 181, Folder 27)
      Route 605, Goochland Co.
    - Job no. 321. (Box 181, Folder 28)
      Beach Road, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 330. (Box 181, Folder 29)
      Route 630, Amelia Co.
    - Job no. 332. (Box 181, Folder 30)
      Howard Drive, Hanover Co.
    - Job no. 333. (Box 181, Folder 31)
      Broad Street Road and Innsbruck Drive, Tuckahoe district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 347. (Box 181, Folder 32)
      Route 625, Goochland Co.
    - Job no. 349. (Box 181, Folder 33)
      Chamberlayne and Azalea Street, Brookland district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 355. (Box 181, Folder 34)
      Otterdale and Old Hundred Road, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 356. (Box 181, Folder 35)
      Richland Road, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 362. (Box 181, Folder 36)
    - Job no. 363. (Box 181, Folder 37)
      Route 643, Hanover Co.
    - Job no. 369. (Box 181, Folder 38)
      Route 663, Caroline Co.
    - Job no. 372. (Box 181, Folder 39)
      Route 703, Hanover Co.
    - Job no. 387. (Box 181, Folder 40)
      Route 603, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 390. (Box 181, Folder 41)
      Walmsley Boulevard, Manchester district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 395. (Box 181, Folder 42)
      Mill Road, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 427. (Box 181, Folder 43)
      Route 654, Hanover Co.
    - Job no. 435. (Box 181, Folder 44)
      Route 360, Midlothian district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 443. (Box 181, Folder 45)
      Kingsland Road, Dale district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 444. (Box 181, Folder 46)
      Temple Avenue, Colonial Heights
    - Job no. 479. (Box 181, Folder 47)
    - Job no. 498. (Box 181, Folder 48)
    - Job no. 542. (Box 182, Folder 1)
      Mechanicsville Turnpike, Route 360, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 554. (Box 182, Folder 2)
      Osborne Road, Varina district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 556. (Box 182, Folder 3)
      Routes 655 and 621, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 624-625. (Box 182, Folder 4)
      South Providence Road, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 635. (Box 182, Folder 5)
      Creighton Road, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 636. (Box 182, Folder 6)
      College Ave., Blacksburg
    - Job no. 645. (Box 182, Folder 7)
      Fordson Road, Three Chopt district, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 645-B. (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - Job no. 676. (Box 182, Folder 9)
      Route 621, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 681. (Box 182, Folder 10)
      17th and Main Streets, Richmond
    - Job no. 691. (Box 182, Folder 11)
      Regester Parkway, Richmond and Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 710. (Box 182, Folder 12)
      Parham Road, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 730. (Box 182, Folder 13)
      Northwood Road, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 739. (Box 182, Folder 14)
      Alvorado and Anoka Roads, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 741. (Box 182, Folder 15)
      Route 360, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 742. (Box 182, Folder 16)
    - Job no. 743. (Box 182, Folder 17)
    - Job no. 746. (Box 182, Folder 18)
      Patterson Avenue and Gayton Road, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 749. (Box 182, Folder 19)
      Route 716, Powhatan Co.
    - Job no. 750. (Box 182, Folder 20)
      North of Route 360, Amelia Co.
    - Job no. 751. (Box 182, Folder 21)
      Dorsey Road, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 752. (Box 182, Folder 22)
      Woolridge Road, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 757. (Box 182, Folder 23)
    - Job no. 773. (Box 182, Folder 24)
      Hull Street Road, Richmond
    - Job no. 780. (Box 182, Folder 25)
    - Job no. 783. (Box 182, Folder 26)
      Dickens Road, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. 784. (Box 182, Folder 27)
      Tomahawk Drive, Clover Hill district, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 811. (Box 182, Folder 28)
      Riverway Road, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. 865. (Box 182, Folder 29)
      Woodpecker Road, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 30)
      Huguenot Road, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 31)
      River Road, Route 602, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 32)
      River Road, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 33)
      Spring Run Road, Chesterfield Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 34)
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 35)
      Chamberlayne Road, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 36)
      Greenwood Road, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 37)
      Indale Avenue, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 38)
      Kingsland Road, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 39)
      Brookhill Azalea Shopping Center, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 40)
      Mooreland Road, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 41)
      Osborne Turnpike and Battlefield Parkway, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 42)
      Sleepy Hollow Road, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 43)
      Westham Parkway, Henrico Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 44)
      Route 607, Nelson Co.
    - Job no. [blank]. (Box 182, Folder 45)
      12th Street, Richmond
    - Zoning ordinance amendments. (Box 182, Folder 46)
      Chesterfield Co.
- Series VII: Foster and Miller files, 1959-1973., Extent: 1 box (.45 cu. ft.). (Box 182a)
  This series contains ten job files from Foster and Miller. Each file folder lists job number, client name, job location, and a record of the field work done. Included are plats, notes on coordinates, topography maps, and information obatined from land title searches (deeds and pre-existing plats).
  Arranged numerically by Job number.
  - Job no. 12615. (Box 182a, Folder 1)
    Whiteside Road, Henrico Co.
  - Job no. 13852. (Box 182a, Folder 2)
    Wistar Road, Henrico Co.
  - Job no. 13964. (Box 182a, Folder 3)
    Ecoff Avenue, Chesterfield Co.
  - Job no. 15476. (Box 182a, Folder 4)
    East Richmond Road, Richmond
  - Job no. 19426. (Box 182a, Folder 5)
    Hull Street Road, Chesterfield Co.
  - Job no. 21573. (Box 182a, Folder 6)
    Old Washington Highway, Henrico Co.
  - Job no. 22342. (Box 182a, Folder 7)
    Whittington Drive, Chesterfield Co.
  - Job no. 22901. (Box 182a, Folder 8)
    Old Locke Lane, Richmond
  - Job no. 23953. (Box 182a, Folder 9)
  - Job no. 33388. (Box 182a, Folder 10)
- Series VIII. Thornton L. Mullins files, 1929-1941., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 183-185b)
  This series includes the files of Thornton L. Mullins, certified civil surveyor in Richmond, Virginia. Mullins worked with LaPrade and was killed on D-Day during World War II. Interspersed within the collection are LaPrade surveys.
  - Subseries 1. Alphabetical files., 2 boxes (2 cu. ft.)
    The bulk of the surveys range from 1929 to 1941, mainly concentrating in Chesterfield and Henrico Counties and Richmond, Virginia. Included are a few surveys from Charles City, Orange, and Warwick Counties, and Newport News. Of note are several files regarding the creation of the Richmond Battlefield Parks and the acquisition of land surrounding the parks. Also included are many subdivision plans for neighborhoods in Chesterfield and Henrico Counties.
    - Charles City Co. (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Chesterfield Co. and Richmond. (Box 183, Folder 2)
      Loch Lomond Gardens subdivision, Bradleys property, Midlothian Turnpike
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 183, Folder 3)
      John C. Temple tract subdivision, near Colonial Heights
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 183, Folder 4)
      Woodlawn
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 183, Folder 5)
      Coleman Wortham tract
    - Chesterfield Co. (Box 183, Folder 6)
      Miscellaneous 1970 annexation, now Richmond, old Manchester district
    - Emporia. (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Goochland Co. (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Hanover Co. (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 10-19)
      Battlefield Park Farms subdivision, Richmond Battlefield Parks Corporation
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 20)
      Chamberlayne Heights subdivision
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 21)
      Chesterman's subdivision
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 22)
      Dumbarton Heights or Wistar Heights
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 23-24)
      Glenbrook Hills
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 25)
      A.A. Harvie, dam near Glen Allen
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 26)
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 27)
      Laurel Heights
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 28)
      Lewis Ginter Land and Improvement Co., sewer easement
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 29)
      Mayfield subdivision, owned by Mr. J. Edmund Massey
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 30)
      McEvory estate, Staples Mill Road
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 31)
      M and K Patterson Avenue adjoining 'Rollingwood'
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 32)
      Moncure, 208 E. Cary St.
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 33)
      Montrose Heights addition
    - Henrico Co. (Box 183, Folder 34)